After the caller is finished crawling, you should see
the status has completed and table change.
The one table change, click on that.
You'll see the tables added as H-V-F-H-V-H-V-F-H-V.
Next, go to the database here under the data catalog.
Go to your database mission, D-H-H-O-F-N-Y-C-T-L-C.
Click on that and then refresh it.
Refresh this display thing here.
You should see the table right here.
In fact, this show the table name.
Click on the table name right here.
You can see that the crawler properly classified the
file as Parquet.
And the table is in our database. Data is in this location.
The table points to two, this location.
And if you scroll down, you can see the schema
that the crawler created, has the column names here
and the data types as well,
which has been accurately captured by the crawler.
There's about 20 fields in the file.
We can then scroll up, scroll up,
and then go to actions right here.
And then click on view data. You'll get a popup like this.
You'll be taken to Athena.
So click on Proceed
and you'll come to this particular Athena console here.
And you're gonna go to query settings
and click on manage right here.
You'll get this particular popup window.
Click on browse three.
You'll see a bucket called as Mission, D-E-H-H-O-F,
Athena Query Results.
Choose your bucket with this name, mission, D-H-H-O-F,
Choose that and then scroll down and save.
This will show up like this right here.
And then scroll up, go back to the editor.
You already have the query here that is auto-populated.
You are gonna come down and click on a run.
So this will show you the data
from the file in the S3 bucket on your query editors
results view.
As such, all the 20 columns
that is saw in the table in blue catalog log, you're able
to view the data in them right here.
So this is how you actually look at the data,
understand the data for your analysis,
and right here it choose data database
that you have called Mission, D-E-H-H-O-F-N-O-C-T-L-C.
And you shoot the table here as well,
and you expand on this.
You should see the columns and the data types here as well.